<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Art</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson</author>
	<url></url>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/AndroidQuazar/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VFEArt</packageId>
    <description>Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Art module is something long overdue. Being an artist, I struggled to comprehend why the only type of sculptures we can make are small, large or grand artworks on a tiny pedestal. It made Artistic skill pretty much undesirable. Come on, how many times have you said to yourself “Oh crikey, that’s another pawn that can only do art”? 

A lot of people requested this mod on my Patreon so it’s about time I deliver. With this mod, your colony can create simple pottery from neolithic times, allowing you to gain some silver on the side to kickstart your base into the medieval era. Several new pieces of sculptures are available by the likes of small, large and grand statues, wall reliefs, decorative pillars and plinths that act both as an artwork and a shelf.

With industrial era your colony will be able to produce beautiful embroidered rugs to decorate those ugly floors! A new type of wall - wallpaper - is now also available, allowing you to put some colour onto your grim, broken walls. Spacer era features a new type of art called a hologram, emitting beautiful shade of blue light and using intellectual skill to determine the quality of it - however it does use up power!

And if that isn’t enough, a new type of quest reward is available - Archotech sculptures, not only being extremely beautiful and desirable, but also imprinting stunning imagery in the minds of surrounding colonists!

</description>
</ModMetaData>